https://www.moviemusic.com/info/privacypolicy/

shopping cart   |  sign in
SEARCH
Home
Random Records!
The Machinist (El Maquinista)
The Brady Bunch Movie
Little Women
Elmer Gantry
Peter Gunn (TV)
Store Info
Happy Customers!
Contact the Store
Like Us!
Follow Us!
MovieMusic Store Privacy Policy
1. GENERAL PRACTICES AND DEFINITIONS
1.1 The MovieMusic Company has created this privacy policy in order to
demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
The following discloses our
information gathering and dissemination practices for The MovieMusic Store.
1.2 Your I.P. (Internet Protocol) address is logged by this site to help diagnose problems with our services
and to administer our web site.
1.3 The MovieMusic Store uses cookie technology for shopping cart functionality.
We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and for other purposes, including, but not limited to,
our community forum (The Lobby).
No personally identifying information is written to cookies stored on a user's machine.
1.4 The MovieMusic Store's account registration form requires users to provide contact information (an
email address).
We use this information to communicate with the user about store business.
Users
may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Users are required to protect their
account with a password of their choice.
1.5 The MovieMusic Store website may contain links to other sites.
The MovieMusic Company is not responsible for the privacy
practices or the content of such web sites.
1.6 The MovieMusic Store uses order forms for customers to
request information, buy products and other services.
We collect customer contact information (like
email addresses and mailing addresses) and financial information (like bank card numbers).
This
information is used to send order updates, confirmations and information about our store and service.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Financial information that is collected is used to bill customers for products and services.
2. COMMUNITY FORUMS
2.1 The MovieMusic Store makes available a community forum (known as The Lobby) to users.
Any information disclosed in this area by users becomes public information.
Caution should be exercised when disclosing personal information in The Lobby.
3. SECURITY
3.1 The MovieMusic Store has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the
information under our control.
Sensitive information such as financial account data is kept in adherence to strict PCI compliance.
4. CHILDREN'S GUIDELINES
4.1 The MovieMusic Store DOES NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent
or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the
information and participation in the activity.
Without prior parental consent, online information
will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes
without prior parental consent
4.2 The MovieMusic Store DOES NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent
4.3 The MovieMusic Store DOES NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent
4.4 The MovieMusic Store DOES NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent
4.5 The MovieMusic Store DOES NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity
5. CHOICE/OPT-OUT
5.1 The MovieMusic Store provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at any point in time
through our "Contact Us" page and through settings in the user's account.
6. CORRECTIONS/UPDATES
6.1 The MovieMusic Store provides users the option for changing and modifying
existing information through our "Contact Us" page and through self-management of a user's account.
Account passwords can only be reset if lost, as they are stored with 1-way encryption.
7. CONTACTING THE COMPANY
7.1 If you have any questions about this privacy policy, Company practices, or dealings with The MovieMusic Store,
please contact us via our "Contact Us" page or via mail:
The MovieMusic Company
415 North Pennsylvania Avenue #4111
Roswell, New Mexico 88202-8572
© 1998-2020, The MovieMusic Company. 415 N Pennsylvania Ave #4111. Roswell, New Mexico USA
